<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RoboMuse 4.0</string>
    <string name="guide">Coming soon</string>
    <string name="about">
        RoboMuse since its inception in 2008 at IIT Delhi under the aegis of Prof S. K. Saha
        has undergone a lot of incremental changes in design and capabilities. The concept of
        RoboMuse was inspired from various competitions held under the umbrella of RoboCon and
        a need was felt to design and develop a mobile robot platform which can be standardized
        for a typical industrial payload or as a research platform which could perform a variety
        of tasks that can be built into it incrementally over the years. While there have been 5
        versions of RoboMuse there has been a lack of standardization in the design of the RoboMuse.
        Thus, the current available research platforms and industry trends were studied in order to
        gauge the features of a research platform and standard specifications and requirements were
        obtained.
        Since, the currently available RoboMuse platforms had to be utilized for future work,
        simulated analysis was carried out in ANSYS on the available RoboMuse platforms namely
        RoboMuse 3XT and RoboMuse 4 to determine the structural integrity and thus the critical
        parts were identified and necessary recommendations for design change for taking the
        increased payload were made. A study to change in drive specifications in order to increase
        the payload carrying capacity of the mobile robot was also carried out which needed change
        in the drive components. The functioning of differential steering system and robot kinematics
        was studied in order to understand the various actions performed by the mobile robot. ROS
        architecture was studied extensively and it was used in running the robot and performing
        experimentation. The actual running of RoboMuse 4 was performed by using various different
        approaches to provide velocity and positional commands to the RoboMuse. There were no
        available International standard for the testing of the mobile robot. Hence, the test
        methods had to be developed for the measurement of mechanical performance parameters. Live
        experimentation is essential in order to determine the performance parameters such as
        repeatability in various tasks, obstacle parameters etc. under real time testing. A number
        of experimentations were thus performed to determine these parameters. It was also possible
        to improve the performance parameters of the RoboMuse significantly by reducing the systematic
        errors by UMB benchmark test. The use of Gazebo as a tool for simulation was made in order
        to simulate the RoboMuse in a simulated environment and various methods of running the
        RoboMuse in simulated environment were demonstrated. Subsequently, simulated applications
        such as surveillance and endurance test were developed on RoboMuse out of which the former
        has been tested and demonstrated successfully in real time. Thus, the experiments may be
        developed, tested and improved in simulated environment first and then be tested in real-time.
    </string>

</resources>
